WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Our world never stops moving,
changing,
evolving.
Every day, we go about our routines.
Work, home, family.
But who are we?
Who am I?
You think you know
your beautiful wife...
your adorable kids...
and who you work for.
But what if you don't?
And the truth...
once you knew it...
would change everything.
Another nightmare?
Yeah. I'm sorry.
Please see someone.
I'm worried about you,
and so are the girls.
I can figure this out.
Wanna hear an even scarier nightmare?
This husband...
refuses to deal with his issues,
and so his wife goes insane
from lack of sleep,
and pushes him out a window.
The end.
Monkey see, monkey do!
Hey, what are you doing?
Playing with monkey.
You can be my assistant.
I can be your assistant?
Well, I'd love to be your assistant,
but I have to get to work on time.
But you know what?
Since we've all been
working really hard lately, right?
Especially Herman.
Especially Herman,
that's what I was thinking.
Why don't I get off of work early
and we can go to the pier?
Does Hanna have to come?
- Hanna does have to come.
- Yeah, your big sister has to come.
But we're gonna force her
to have a good time,
and if not... I'll show you.
I'll show you what we're gonna do.
No, no!
Stop, stop, stop!
Speaking of which, uh, where is she?
- One guess.
- Oh.
- Bye, Daddy.
- Bye, Luce.
Oh, and Samantha keeps asking
when we're gonna have that party
to celebrate my work thing.
Oh, yeah, um...
- Let's do it tomorrow.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm beginning to forget
what our friends look like.
Ha-ha.
- Love you.
- You too.
The pier!
Good morning. Lobby?
Yes, please.
It's nice weather outside.
No talking while the elevator
is in motion, please.
Oh, that's right.
Okay.
Oh, look at that, perfect timing.
- Pete.
- Hey.
Ms. Elevator Person.
How's the j-o-b?
Just a cog in the machine, sir.
I'd complain to corporate,
but who would listen?
Thank you, miss.
Hey, Mr. Wright?
Can I come see Maggie later?
Totally. Hey, we've got
a new sound system set up.
- Dance party time!
- Awesome!
Actually, tonight we were planning
on family night.
Okay, cool. Another time.
Enjoy!
What are you trying to do?
Wait, wait! No, no!
Wait, wait, wait!
I know I've been out of it
these last couple weeks.
Weeks?
That was a good insult.
Thank you.
Can we please spend time as a family?
I really want to make
it up to you guys.
So what are we gonna do?
I don't know.
Guess you're just gonna
have to go upstairs and find out.
God dammit!
Reset.
Wow. I don't remember the last time
I saw you crash a machine.
The current split
and blew up both the systems.
Sleeping okay?
Yeah. Well, better.
You know, it's funny,
I was talking to somebody
and they were telling me
about this clinic that people go to...
for, you know,
sleeplessness and stress.
I could get you the number.
- I'm just trying...
- No, no. It's just a little mistake.
I'm gonna fix it.
Sure. I got you.
Okay.
- Let me know if you need anything.
- Okay.
Oh, um... David?
Is there any way I could...
take off early today?
Will you call the number for me?
Yeah.
All right.
The aim would be to update
the drainage systems
along Prescott, Calder, and Willow.
Now, I believe that if we focus
on the tunnels beneath these streets,
we could reduce overall runoff
in the city's west side by up to 30%.
Thank you all so much.
That's all for today.
They should have done the upgrade
years ago.
Hey, that was great, Al.
- Thank you.
- Not at all.
It makes me look good
for promoting you.
You want to work late tonight,
talk about how to get this over
the line with Water and Power?
Oh, I-I was actually going to ask you
if I could leave early today.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
'WHOLE LIFE'
WELLNESS CENTER
If we gave them a chance,
maybe they could be of
benefit to the planet.
Besides, whether we like it or not,
they're here to stay,
so we should entertain
the possibility
they be given the same rights
as you and I.
Same rights as you and I?
They have no rights.
At some point, they will rise up,
they will overtake us,
they will subdue us.
Okay? They will conquer humanity.
I don't mean to be alarmist,
but it's happening,
we see it happening,
and we need to take action now!
Alice!
Do you-- do you see that?
Do you see that light?
That light?
CITY ANTIQUES
He probably
just had to stay late at work.
You don't need to
make excuses for him.
You have the right to be upset
with him, honey.
He should have called.
He loves you, you know that.
Yeah, I know.
Good night.
Hey, I'm really sorry.
- I see you got time to go shopping.
- Oh, I got this for the girls.
Sure you did.
- Can you just give me a break?
- A break? From what, exactly?
- From me? Or the girls?
- That's not what I'm saying.
Okay, well, it sure as hell
is what you're doing.
I had one of those nightmares,
today... at work.
I passed out,
and that's why I'm late.
Peter, I...
I am worried about you, okay?
I know.
This is me, this is your daughters,
they're worried about you too.
I don't...
understand why you won't
just get some help.
They're just gonna
say it's in my head.
Because it is just in your head.
Mommy?
Why were you guys yelling?
It's okay, baby. Come on.
Everything's fine.
Mommy, wake up.
Mommy, please, wake up.
Please.
Mommy, wake up.
Mommy, please, wake up.
- Girls!
- No, no, no, no! Stop!
Girls!
Hey, girls! Girls!
Stop for a second, please.
- Have you seen my briefcase anywhere?
- No!
'WHOLE LIFE'
WELLNESS CENTER
Morning, girls.
Can we talk about last night?
Hanna...
Hey, I'm sorry.
Hey, what's up with Herman?
- He won't talk anymore.
- Yeah?
Maybe he's mad at you.
Oh.
Well...
he has every right to be.
Hey, Luce, can I talk to Herman?
Herman, I understand
your frustration,
and...
while an apology isn't fix-all,
I am sorry that I
missed family night.
If you want,
I can take a look at him,
see if there's anything I can do
about that voice.
When's he gonna talk again?
I think if we just reroute
one of these wires...
All right, Herman, what do you say?
Monkey see, monkey do!
Thanks, Dad.
I called that doctor.
She's gonna see me after work today.
Really?
Yup. You bet.
Here at Whole Life,
your mental health
is our number one priority.
Become the best you you can be,
with our discreet and
expert services,
provided at no cost to you,
in the interest of a happy
and healthy society.
What do you see?
I'm sorry, what?
You're having trouble sleeping,
right?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Well, something's coming.
What do you mean something's coming?
The lights.
Yeah, up above.
All the people running...
dying.
Do you see anyone you care about?
We're not alone.
But they... they don't want us
to know what's coming.
They want to control us,
don't want us asking questions.
That's why they erase our thoughts,
because if we knew what was coming...
- Chaos.
- Chris.
Do you want to come through?
We're not crazy.
I just...
I need this to stop.
Planet evacuation in progress.
They'll be back.
I'll meet you back at the factory.
How was it?
I went...
And what'd they say?
Well...
She didn't get to say anything.
I left before the appointment.
Just hear me out.
What if I'm meant
to be seeing these things?
Or having these dreams?
What if something bad is coming...
and this is like a sign?
Stop. Just...
Our friends will be here soon,
please make an effort.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
'Hurricane' plays ♫
♪ Didn't know what this would be ♪
♪ But I knew I didn't see ♪
♪ What you thought you saw in me ♪
♪ I jumped the gun ♪
♪ So sure you'd split and run... ♪
The tunnel system is so old,
no one else would take it on,
that's all.
This promotion is a big deal, Al.
You should be happy.
- I am.
- Good.
Hey, hey...
Don't you worry about him.
It's your night, okay?
I know.
- Mom?
- Yes?
Daddy said to ask you
if I can take Hanna and
Lucy to our place.
- Why?
- To play music.
Oh, no, honey.
It's rude to leave. Okay?
♪ Welcome to the inner workings
Of my mind ♪
♪ So dark and foul I can't disguise ♪
♪ Nights like this ♪
♪ I become afraid ♪
♪ Of the darkness in my heart ♪
♪ Hurricane ♪
Good night!
Last few guests are taking off,
in case you wanted to say goodbye.
Or hello.
Did my wife send you over?
No, worse. My wife.
You know,
I like to look up sometimes.
It puts everything in perspective,
don't you think?
What do you really want to ask?
I know it's none of my business.
I think you're looking
in the wrong direction.
I mean, you're out here
focused on whatever's up there,
when you should be looking
at what's in there.
I am.
What the hell is that?
You see that?
You kidding? Of course I can.
What is that?
You okay?
What the hell was that?
Everyone, get inside! Now!
The girls! Hanna!
Megan!
Hanna!
- Megan!
- Hanna!
Hey! Hey!
Where's your sister?
- I want Mommy!
- I know, I know, I know. Alice!
- Lucy!
- Mommy!
- Come here, baby.
- Where's your sister?
- They have to be at our place.
- Stay with Lucy!
I'll find Hanna and bring her back.
It's okay. It'll be okay.
This is an emergency broadcast.
Please make your way
to the nearest government facility
in order to ensure your safety.
This is an emergency broadcast.
Please make your way
to the nearest government facility
in order to ensure your safety.
This is an emergency broadcast.
Megan!
- Hanna!
- Megan!
Hanna!
Get down!
They're not here.
I know where they are.
Oh, no.
Whatever's in those ships
must be in the building.
Megan, are you in there?
Hanna, are you there?
Hanna!
Come on, we gotta get down there.
Come on!
Hurry!
Dad! What's happening?
- Come on, baby. I gotcha.
- Daddy!
Hurry up, we gotta get out of here!
Okay, come on.
Daddy's got you, baby.
Come on. There you go. There you go.
Let's go.
- Where's Mom and Lucy?
- They're safe. They're safe.
It's clear. Pass them up.
Stop. Go and look.
It's okay.
- Okay! Let's go!
- You see anything?
Let's go! Come on! Come on!
Hanna! Are you okay?
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
- Lucy! Oh, God.
- Let's go.
Come on, hurry.
Okay, get under the table.
Ray went to get Sam
and then they're gonna meet us here.
- Okay. It's okay.
- Hey, can I talk to you for a second?
- There's some things in the building.
- In your nightmares,
this is what you saw?
- Yes, it's what I saw!
- Then what do we do?
What happens in the dream?
What happens next?
What do we do?
In the dream...
they're not in order.
And I saw David.
I feel like we should
go to the factory.
Okay.
Ray and Sam should've been here
by now, right?
We need to barricade the door.
- With what?
- Peter, come on.
All right. Come on, girls. Come on.
I have to go help your dad, okay?
So, Hanna, I need you
to look after your sister.
- All right?
- Don't leave!
It's okay, baby.
Alice!
I'll be right back.
You stay here, okay?
Do not open the door.
God, I love you both so much.
Okay.
What are you doing?
- Herman!
- Lucy! Come back!
Go, go!
Where's your sister?
She went looking for Herman.
Monkey see, monkey do!
I'm not afraid of your shadow.
You can't hurt me.
Lucy!
Come here!
Mommy!
Watch out! Girls!
Come over here. Come over here.
All right, let's go before more come.
Okay, come on.
Come on.
Keep your eyes closed.
Close your eyes.
There's more of them?
They're moving up
through the building.
They're all through.
Stay here.
Daddy, don't go!
No, no, no! Stay!
You scared the hell out of us, man.
Where are the girls?
Alice, it's safe.
Okay, come on. Come on.
Oh, my God.
Lucy, Hanna!
Lucy!
Megan, where have you been?
What's happening?
What is happening?
We'll be safe up here,
- right?
- Just stay close to me.
Who are they?
Why are they doing this?
Those people!
What do we do?
I don't know.
Get down!
Mommy!
What's happening?
Hey, Alice. We can't stay up here.
- Come on, Lucy.
- Let's get out of here.
- Okay, come on. Stay calm.
- Where are we going?
- Don't let go of each other's hands.
I think we can use this
to get down.
- We should use this.
- What? No.
- Alice!
- No! No.
- I'm not putting the girls on that.
- Alice!
- No! I'm not getting in there.
- We need to get off this roof.
If it's between taking the girls
through the building
- or putting them in that thing...
- If we stay here, we die.
If we go through the building,
we die.
Just trust me, please.
I need you to trust me.
We haven't got time for this.
This is gonna work. Let's go.
No!
- I don't wanna go down there!
- It's okay, come on.
- Okay, okay.
- No!
Okay.
- Come on. Come with us.
- Get her down.
I don't wanna go, Mommy!
Baby...
Oh, Mommy, I'm scared!
I don't like it up here, Mommy.
What's happening?
Mommy!
I got you, I got you!
- Hold on, hold on!
- Nobody move.
- I wanna get off!
- Don't move!
We gotta go in.
No! Lucy, don't look down!
Go on, Lucy. Come on.
Come on! Go, go, go!
- Hanna, let's go.
- They could be in there!
Hanna, we have to go!
Quick, quick!
- Grab on!
- Go, go!
HANNA * LUCY * HERMAN
Here. I found a flashlight.
Don't turn it on, okay?
In the dreams...
did you see them kill us?
Did you see them kill our girls?
Mommy, wake up.
Mommy, please wake up.
Peter, you have to tell me.
Hey, any luck with this?
Um, the technology's
not much different than ours,
but it's got a biometric trigger,
which can only be shot by its owner.
Can you bypass it or something?
I'm working on it.
Either way, I don't think
we should stay here much longer.
No, I think we need
to leave the city.
- Find some place to hide.
- Wait for help.
Wait, wait...
The factory I work at,
it's not far from here...
and it's a government building.
And it's, uh... it's right there.
It's like...
it's about ten blocks away.
Is it safe?
How do we know anywhere
is safe right now?
Because of what's underneath it.
It's all storage space.
It's like a fortress down there.
I mean, it's just getting there.
Yeah, they're still firing
at anything that moves.
Unfortunately,
that's our only chance.
The tunnels.
The tunnels, there's the entrance...
What street?
There's the opening on...
- Prescott!
- On Prescott!
That's only a few
blocks from here.
We can get to the factory
through the tunnels.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
- We can make it a few blocks, right?
- Yeah.
Dad!
Daddy!
Lucy!
Come on, let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
This way! Come here!
Move it! Oh, shit! Get down!
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Dad!
- All right, let's move.
- No, not there!
The factory's ten blocks away,
we're gonna be safe.
We're not going
to let anything happen to you.
Okay? To either of you.
- Okay?
- Let's go, let's go!
- Okay? Come on.
- Let's go!
Are we gonna die
like Megan's family?
Don't worry, honey,
you'll be safe.
Come on, come on. Lucy.
Please, stop!
- Who are they?
- I don't know.
Go! Go, go! Get down!
Stay down. Stay down.
- Let's go, let's go, let's go!
- Come on!
- Come on, run!
- Go, go, go!
Run, run, run!
Up here.
- Come on.
- Where should we go?
It's to the right.
Okay...
On the other side of the plants.
Okay, I'll go first.
Stay down.
Go, hurry.
Here, get up. We have to be quick.
Okay, come here. Come here.
Okay, be careful. Be careful.
Stay right there. Stay right there.
- Come on.
- Go. Go to Dad.
Lucy! Lucy!
Lucy, come here!
Take her!
Come on!
Let's go! Let's go!
Is everyone okay?
You okay?
Mom?
Dad?
Do something.
Mommy...
It's okay, baby.
Okay, watch your step.
There we go.
Okay, which way?
We're under the park.
North. Okay.
Come on, girls.
What happens from here?
- Did you see this?
- Not like this.
Promise me that you're going...
to protect the girls.
No matter what happens.
Okay?
- Alice...
- Just promise me.
I don't want to do this
without you, please.
Please, I don't want to.
Please... promise.
- Promise...
- I know you can do it.
Come on, you can do it.
- Please.
- Okay.
There you go, there you go.
Yes.
There we go, that's my Alice.
That's my Alice.
I need to sit.
No problem. Okay, okay.
Okay.
Here.
Rub her hands.
- Is she gonna be okay?
- Yes, she's gonna be fine.
Keep them warm.
You're doing okay.
Let her rest, it's fine. It's okay.
- It's okay.
- Daddy!
Leave my daddy alone!
Daddy, I'm scared.
Just stay there.
Why are you here?
You want to hurt my family?
Is that what you want?
What...
Who are you?
Why are you doing this?
Mom?
She-- she won't wake up!
Mom, wake up! Mom!
- Say something!
- Mom!
- Mom, come on, wake up!
- Daddy, help!
Mommy!
Let's get her up. Let's get Mommy up.
Girls, get behind me.
Get behind me, girls.
Get behind me. Lucy, get behind me.
Pick her up.
Do you understand me?
Pick her up right now.
And I want you to move slow.
Hello?
Maybe one of the other doors.
Mom needs help now.
No, no.
- Oh, here, here.
- Here. Move!
No, no, no!
Please, please! Please, no, no!
No, no, no, please.
That's my wife, she's in bad shape.
We need help.
Peter?
- David.
- Hold up, hold up!
- Hey.
- You got one.
Alice, she's in bad shape right now,
she needs help right away.
Hey, gurney! Right now!
Yes, sir! Coming through.
She was hit on the
left side really bad.
Any other injuries?
- Not that I...
- Dad!
They're coming.
Everybody, inside, now!
Hold her steady.
Go ahead.
- Scan her.
- You got to stop the bleeding.
What is that?
- Stop!
- Stop it!
Wait, what are you doing?
It's okay. It's a diagnostic.
He knows what he's doing.
Stop! I said stop!
Don't touch her! Stop!
- You're hurting her!
- I told you to stop!
- Everybody just calm down.
- What the hell's going on?
We're all friends here, all right?
Mommy! Stop it!
Why does it feel
like you're prepared for this?
What's happening out there has been
headed our way for a long time.
But right now,
let's please focus on your wife
and getting you and
your family to safety.
Please.
There's an abandoned train station
below us.
Headed to an underground base
where we've been stockpiling weapons.
- What happened to all the storage?
- Sent ahead. We'll be safe.
They'll never find us.
Once we're there,
we'll finalize our plan to fight back.
But I'm not a soldier.
You'd be surprised
what you're capable of.
They're directly above us.
They're gonna get through.
Okay. Prepare for a breach
and get everyone downstairs now.
- Yes, sir.
- Get rid of him.
- Take him out back and kill him.
- It's your wife...
The damage is way beyond
our ability to repair.
If she can make it
through the evacuation,
she might have a chance,
but her system's shutting down.
- There's nothing we can do.
- There's gotta be a way to help her.
I'm sorry, we don't
have the equipment.
Wait! No, no!
- You can't quit on Mom.
- Nobody's quitting on Mom.
Hey, I can help her!
I can help her!
I can help her, man!
I can keep her going!
What?
I can keep her alive,
keep her going!
You can keep her going?
- You trying to play games with me?
- I'm not.
You our enemy? The medic said
he can't help her, and you can?
I can keep her going long enough
to get help.
- Why should I believe you?
- He's lying.
- We have to go.
- It's not true.
I had to learn everything about
your people, all right? There's ways.
There's no time. We have to evacuate
right now. Get him out of here!
- Go!
- I know what to do!
- Let's go!
- Let me help!
Okay, stop, stop! Stop!
Okay, girls, girls.
Okay, you have to listen to me.
You have to listen, okay?
- You're going with David.
- No!
I'm gonna stay with Mom
until she's good,
and then I'm gonna join you guys,
I promise.
We'll meet you at the train.
Okay.
The evacuation transport
is downstairs.
- We'll hold as long as we can.
- Okay.
Girls, girls, girls, please, please.
- Know that I love you, okay?
- No!
Dad!
No!
- Stop!
- Daddy! Dad!
You got time?
Move, move!
All the way down the back.
Let's go!
Give me a knife
and bring those lights over here.
Stop. Here you go.
All right.
Hey! Easy! Easy, easy, please!
- Easy!
- You want me to do this?
I'm trying to help you!
All right. Oh, shit.
They're right, it's bad.
What is that? What is that?
What's in her?
What is that? What is in her?
You really don't know what...
you are?
Look, if you want to save her life,
she's gonna need
an alternative source of power.
I'm talking about you.
Hanna!
I lost Herman!
Okay.
Put the... put the knife down.
And...
go over there.
Okay. All right, what do I do?
You got to...
You got to make an incision...
on your chest,
at a sideways edge.
Okay. Okay.
Start at the top.
Just make a straight line,
about six inches across.
I should warn you...
if this doesn't work...
the current will split and...
then you're both dead.
Let's do it.
Synthetics will take over the world.
A.I. will take over the world.
Does that not scare you, that they're
starting to wake up to the idea
that they were designed to serve us?
We are not God, but we are their god
because we created them
and that makes us their god.
And that gives us the right
to do with them whatever we want to.
If we want to shut them down,
we can shut them down.
Genocides have
always been about one race
thinking they're better
than the other race..
What makes us better
than the synthetics?
The previous genocides in history
were against human beings,
not against created objects,
not against can openers.
Pick up your shit,
you stupid synth!
The late Stephen Hawking,
he said that A.I.
would be the downfall of mankind.
I mean, does that not terrify you?
Are they not starting
to exhibit lifelike tendencies
that would compel them to wonder
why they were built
in the first place?
Why did you do that?
I don't know.
You will not replace us!
So what's next?
Welfare payments?
The right to marry?
Where does it stop?
They're taking our jobs,
endangering our lives.
Just last week, a synthetic
hospitalized a human.
It was self-defense.
It's well-reported,
a group of humans attacked
a synthetic with
no provocation at all.
You will not replace us!
- You will not replace us!
- What's going to happen to us?
You will not replace us!
Fighting, defensive or otherwise,
is the result of emotion.
If they're beginning
to experience any emotion,
the ultimate consequence
will be devastating for society.
We need to round them up
and shut them down
by any means necessary!
Alice!
- They sent the military?
- The decommission has started.
They want to wipe us out.
We got to get out of here.
- They're coming!
- Okay.
No!
Enough!
Come on.
I'm sorry.
I had to do it.
I know. I know.
Here, take it.
You have to defend yourself.
All units, report
to your nearest marked
shuttle station.
Planet evacuation in progress.
All units, report to your nearest
marked shuttle station.
Planet evacuation in progress.
All units, report to your nearest
marked shuttle station.
Planet evacuation in progress.
All units, report to your nearest
marked shuttle station.
Planet evacuation in progress.
All units, report to your nearest
marked shuttle station.
Planet evacuation in progress.
Sweep's clean, no humans.
All right, everyone fall out.
Head back to your posts.
That's gotta be the last of them.
They'll be back.
Never trust a human to
just let things be.
Some of us are gonna
have to stay ready.
I'll meet you back at the factory.
We should go.
Wait.
Hey. Come here.
- Whoa.
- Hey, hey.
Leave us alone.
I'll shoot you.
It's okay.
It's okay. We're the same as you.
We're the same as you.
Hey...
it's okay. Give me the gun.
Just give me the gun.
It's okay.
Here I go.
We're not gonna hurt you.
Are you guys here alone?
They killed Mom and Dad
because they were human.
You'll no longer
have to live in fear.
The memories of the past
will be replaced.
And you will be a family.
- Alice.
- Careful.
The cord's the only thing
keeping her alive right now.
Okay, she's...
she's breathing better, that's good.
- That's good.
- Wouldn't call it "breathing."
It worked.
I don't know how long
it'll hold up, but...
It worked.
I remember...
the-- the war.
You guys tried to wipe us out.
We chose to forget. Must be nice...
picking what memories you can keep.
Humans don't have that luxury.
Why are you helping us?
You could have killed us
when I was passed out.
It was my grandparents
you chased off the planet.
I wasn't even born yet.
It was like 50 years ago.
We've been living in colonies
on Mars since.
None of us had even
been to Earth before.
We didn't know what to expect.
Didn't even know
if we could still breathe down here.
We did learn everything
about you...
the synthetics.
How you drove us from our homes
and left us with nothing.
It took us all this
time just to gather
the resources we
needed to come back.
They told us you were monsters.
Savages.
It's kind of just one
side of the story.
I know that now.
So why am I helping you?
'Cause no one said I'd be coming
down here killing kids...
and families.
It's not what I signed up for.
Peter.
Baby! Baby?
- Hey, you're doing well.
- I saw...
I saw... I--I saw...
I saw... I...
Your dreams... it's the past.
It's our past.
- The dreams.
- Yeah.
Those girls... the girls!
No, no, they're waiting for us.
Planet evacuation in progress.
Proceed to the platform
in an orderly fashion, please,
and board the train.
We can't wait any longer.
As soon as David gets here,
we're gone.
Last train!
Move, move, move!
- Lucy, come on.
- Not without Mommy and Daddy!
- Come on.
- They'll be here! Daddy said that!
This is a Level Three
mandatory evacuation.
Follow evacuation protocol.
Proceed to the platform
in an orderly fashion, please,
and board the train.
You guys got to hide.
I'll tell them I'm alone
when they get in here, but...
- I don't know, it's your only shot.
- We gotta get back to the girls.
All right.
Come on. It's okay.
You all right?
I'm-- I'm Peter.
Miles.
Here. You know what? Here.
It was never mine to begin with,
but thank you.
Are you guys okay?
- Yes.
- Yeah, yeah.
Okay, stay tight and low.
Cover, now! Go, go, go!
- Move!
- Go!
Go, go, go!
Quickly! Go, go!
Cover us! Cover us!
I'll cover you!
Go for the tunnel. I'll cover you.
Go. Go!
Come on!
How will they get in?
Cover me!
Okay, look.
I need you girls
to get onto the transport now.
- We have to wait.
- Please!
They'll be here.
- No!
- Get off me!
- Stop! Please!
- No!
Let me go!
Come on.
Come on, this way.
Wait! Wait!
Stop, stop!
Hey!
- Come on. Come on.
- Wait!
- Wait.
Hanna!
- Lucy!
- Mommy!
- Hey!
- Daddy!
- Come on!
- Come on, come on!
I knew you'd save her.
Be right back. Come here.
Come here.
You remember?
Yeah. Do they?
Like you,
they had their memories wiped...
to start clean...
without fear,
free of the guilt of...
what we had to do...
just to be free.
A few of us like me
kept our memories,
so we could prepare
for this day.
But now they're all
gonna have to remember,
'cause this...
this is not over.
We'll be safe
at our underground base for now.
There, we'll finalize our plans
to take back home.
So be ready.
I thought I lost you.
Sorry that I didn't believe you.
Our world...
keeps moving...
changing...
evolving...
and so do we.
I know who I am now...
and I know my enemy.
We're not that different.
Maybe...
if others can see that...
we'll have a future after all.
'Don't Wake Me Up'
by The Newton Brothers plays ♫
♪ I'm sinking ♪
♪ I'm falling ♪
♪ You lit us on fire
Then walked away ♪
♪ Left me for dead
Left me in chains ♪
♪ I'm not a fighter,
We're not the same ♪
♪ But when this ends
You're gonna know my name ♪
♪ I lost my composure
I lost my way ♪
♪ I left you for dead
I left you here in chains ♪
♪ The nightmare is over
That's what you said ♪
♪ But I'm scared sober
and wide awake ♪
♪ Out of my way ♪
♪ I'm king of the world ♪
♪ Just for today ♪
♪ Until it all burns ♪
♪ Don't wake me up ♪
♪ Show them it's real ♪
♪ And never enough ♪
♪ Never enough ♪
♪ Millions fought
Everything changed ♪
♪ I don't even recognize my face ♪
♪ Without warning
I lost faith ♪
♪ Just like that
The future turned grey ♪
♪ Out of my way ♪
♪ I'm king of the world ♪
♪ Just for today ♪
♪ Until it all burns ♪
♪ Don't wake me up ♪
♪ Show them it's real ♪
♪ Never enough ♪ ♪ Never enough ♪
♪ These days rush by ♪
♪ I wonder why ♪
♪ I just can't find ♪
♪ Any peace ♪
♪ These days rush by ♪
♪ I wonder ♪
♪ Out of my way ♪
♪ I'm king of the world ♪
♪ Just for today ♪
♪ Until it all burns ♪
♪ Out of my way ♪
♪ I'm king of the world ♪
♪ Just for today ♪
♪ Until it all burns ♪
♪ Don't wake me up ♪
♪ Show them it's real ♪
♪ Never enough ♪
♪ Out of my way ♪
♪ I'm king of the world ♪
♪ Just for today ♪
♪ Until it all burns ♪
♪ Don't wake me up ♪
♪ Show them it's real ♪
♪ Never enough ♪